nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
Surprised.
びっくり
Oh, are you an idol?
え、アイドルですか?
No, I'm not an idol.
いや、アイドルじゃないです
Oh, isn't it?
あ、じゃないの?
That's a lie.
嘘だ
It's not a lie.
嘘じゃない
There's the Sakamichi family, right?
坂道家いるでしょ
There aren't any.
いないですよ
not present?
いない?
It looks amazing.
め っちゃいそう
Not told?
言われない?
Well, I won't say it.
え、言われないです
Don't people say you look like an idol?
アイドルっぽいねって言われない?
Won't you tell me not to make you an idol?
アイドルにしないよって言われない?
I was told that I should be in Akihabara.
なんか、秋葉原に居そうって言われる
They told me to stay in Akihabara.
秋葉原に居そうって言われる
Is it the clothes?
服装なのかな?
Her hairstyle isn't very tight either,
髪型も結構パッツンじゃないけど、
In Russia, I often feel a little like a young lady.
ロシアでなんかちょっと お嬢様感ってよく、
I guess that's what it feels like because it has a clean feel to it.
清素感があるから、 そんな感じなのかなって
Are you actually quite a young lady?
実際結構お嬢様だったりするんですか?
No, not at all.
いやいや、全然そんなことない
It seems so.
そうらしいですね
Well, the camera is already rolling,
で、もうカメラ回っちゃってるんですけど、
What do you think?
どうですかね?
It's shown on a solid camera like this,
こんな、 しっかりしたカメラで 映されてますけど、
What do you think?
なんか どうですか?
I mean, it's a feeling.
気持ちというか
feeling?
気持ち?
I feel nervous.
なんか、緊張する
get nervous?
緊張する?
That's right.
そうだよね
It's like this, I'm still just talking,
こういう感じの、 まだ喋ってるだけですけど、
Is there anything about being filmed like this on camera?
こういう感じでカメラで撮られてるっていう分はありますか?
What is your experience?
経 験は?
No.
ないです
I think you'll be nervous then.
じゃあ緊張すると思うんですけど、
By the way, first of all, I would like to ask you something.
ちなみに最初にね、 ちょっと聞いときたい
What are you going to do in front of this camera today?
今日はこのカメラの前にどんなことをするんですか?
Are you in front of the camera today?
今日はカメラの前で?
Match?
一致する?
Hayate?
はやて?
I can't help but listen to it.
ちょっと聞きづてならない
I want you to hear the words I can't stop hearing.
聞きづつならない言葉を聞いてほしいわ、
now.
今
In front of the camera?
カ メラの前で?
Match in front of the camera.
カメラの前で、 一致する
No.
違います
In front of the camera.
カメラの前でね
Well then, I contacted you on SNS a little bit in advance.
では、ちょっと事前にSNSの方で ご連絡させていただいてて、
This is what it feels like in front of the camera,
カメラの前でって こういう感じなんですけど、
It's not a normal experience.
普通の経験ないですよね
yes.
はい
By the way, I wish I could tell you this.
ちなみにね、 これ伝えられたらいいんですけど、
I do things like this quite a lot,
僕、 結構 こういう感じでやってて、
Why are we shooting like this today?
なんで今日こういう 撮影というか、
If there was a reason why you came to this place,
こういう場所に 来ていただけたのかなっていう 理由があれば、
Tuition fee...
学 費...
Tuition fees?
学費?
Are you a student now?
今、学生さんなんですか?
I see, I'm having a bit of a problem with tuition fees.
なるほど、学費が ちょっと困ってて、
That's what it feels like.
という感じですね
I usually do quite a lot.
僕 は普段、 結構多いんですよ
In this day and age, we need to increase taxes.
このご時世ですから、 増税に増税でね
Well, I don't think that's all.
まあ、それだけじゃないと思うけど、
Isn't it a recession?
不景気じゃないですか
There are many people in trouble.
困っている人多いんですよ
Especially for students.
特に学生さんのとこ
I usually help out, but
僕は普段お助けしてて、 やってますけど、
By the way, which school are you currently attending?
ちなみに、 今どこの学校通われてますか?
is a secret.
は、秘密です
Tell me.
教えてよ
secret?
秘密?
Can't you say it?
言えない?
I can't say it.
言えない
why?
なんで?
My body exposed?
身バレ?
Because you'll find out.
バレちゃうから
I won't find out.
バレない
I'll find out.
バレちゃう
Is there a ban on revealing your identity?
結構身バレ禁裁でますか?
Well, that's true.
まあ、そうですよね
Can you tell me how old you are?
何年生か言える?
I'm a first year student.
1年生です
University?
大学?
Yes, university.
はい、大学
Are you a first year student?
1年生ですか?
1st year student.
1年生
young.
若い
Is it just starting now?
時期的にまだ入ったばっかり?
oh dear.
まあ
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
So, until recently, were you wearing a uniform?
じゃあ、ちょっと前までは 制服?
That's right.
そうですよ
He was wearing a uniform.
制服を着ていました
Oh, seriously?
あ、マジ?
Were you wearing it?
着てたの?
Okay, what's the length of the skirt?
結構、 スカートの丈は どんな感じになってる?
picture?
え?
height?
丈?
But it's somewhere in the middle.
でも、中間ぐらい
Really.
本当 に
A little above the knees.
ちょい膝上とか
A little above the knee?
ちょい膝上?
It's too long below the knees, so it's a little above the knees.
膝下は長すぎるから、 ちょっと膝上
Isn't it quite short now?
今結構短いんじゃない?
Now, that's already the case.
今はもう、 もう そんな
I don't care.
気にしない
Don't you care?
気にしない?
Even first-year students have trouble paying tuition...
1年生でも学費困られ...
Well then, I'm sorry.
じゃあ、ちょっとごめんね
I guess this is where I need to jump in.
突っ込んじゃいけないところかな
A little more at home.
ちょっとご家庭のほうが
I agree.
そうですね
Is that so?
そうかそうか
I see.
なるほどね
Are you currently working part-time?
なんか、今バイトとかされてるんですか?
As for my part-time job, I work at a maid cafe.
バイトは、 メイドカフェで働いてます
Ah, a maid cafe.
あ、メイドカフェ
What is a maid cafe?
メイドカフェってどうなんですか?
I mean hourly wage.
時給というか
Looks pretty good.
結構良さそう
But surprisingly, it's not that expensive.
でも意外と、 そんなに高くないです
Is that so?
そうなの?
I'm a little confused.
ちょっと困ってます
Well then, I'll help you.
じゃあ、 俺が助けてあげるんだけど、
What will the person who helps me say about me?
俺助けてあげる人、 俺のこと、 なんて言う?
What do you say?
なんて言う?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Help me, I want to have fun too.
俺と助けてさ、 俺も楽しみたいからさ、
Just a moment today as a maid, as a maid?
ちょっと今日メイドさんとして、 メイドさんとして?
What do you say about your customers?
お客さんのこと、なんて言ってる?
What about your customers?
お客さんのこと?
A customer or a master?
お客様とか、 ご主人様とか?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだよね
Today, I asked you to call me master.
今日ちょっとさ、 俺のこと、 ご主人様って言ってもらって
good?
いい?
Master?
ご 主人様?
Even though I don't say it at all.
全然言わないのに
Tell me today.
今日は言ってよ
Today is?
今日は?
Do you have a moe-moe-kyun thing?
萌え萌えキュンとかしてるの?
Do you like Moe Moe Kyun?
萌え萌えキュンとかする?
I don't do moe-moe-kyun.
萌え萌えキュンはしない
do not?
しない?
I do it a little bit for fun, but...
なんか、ちょっと遊びでやったりとかはするけど、
I wonder if there's something like that from the store.
お店からして、 して、みたいなのないかな
do not have?
ない?
Actually, I was just having fun, too.
実は今のさ、 俺もちょっと遊びでさ、
I'd like you to do something, but I'm going to do something a little naughty today.
してほしいんだけどさ、 今日ちょっとエッチなことするじゃない
Is it?
ですか
I think you can see it a little now,
今 ちょっと見えてると思うけど、
I'm not feeling well yet and I want you to give me some power.
まだ元気なくて、 パワーを与えてほしいんですよ
You can't do that when this place gets bigger, right?
ここが大きくなったらできないでしょ?
Heading here,
ここに向かって、
Can't you erase it?
消 せんの?
Moe Moe Kyun
萌え萌えキュン
amazing!
すごい!
Too weak!
弱 すぎる!
In an instant!
一瞬で!
Moe-kyun in an instant!
一瞬で萌え萌えキュン!
strange!
おかしい!
Maids have this kind of power! They have this kind of power!
メイドさんにはこんなパワーが こんなパワーがあるんだよ!
terrible!
恐ろしい!
Too scary!
恐ろすぎる!
Too scary?
恐 ろしすぎる?
Surprise!
びっくり!
Now that I've received power, Gumocho has a lot of hustle today.
今 パワーもらったんで、 グモチョウの今日 いっぱいハッサル
I did it.
した いと
Hussar?
ハ ッサル?
Can you do it?
できるかな?
I get so excited when I get so many moe moments.
いっぱい萌え萌えしてもらって、 僕がキュンキュンする
terrible!
やばい!
Too dangerous!
やばすぎる!
Well, since this is a photoshoot, I'd like to ask you something.
じゃあさ、こういう撮影なんで、 ちょっとなんていうか聞いとき
I want to, but what should I do?
たい んですけど、 ぶ っちゃけどうすか?
Do you like or dislike naughty things?
エッチなことは好きか嫌いか、どっちですか?
Do you like it or dislike it?
好きか嫌いか?
picture?
え?
secret!
秘密!
I like that.
ってことは好きだね
What, do you masturbate?
え、オナニとかする?
Masturbation...
オナニは...
Do you know what masturbation is?
オナニって分かる?
meaning?
意味?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
By myself...
自分で...
touch?
触る?
Where do you touch it?
どこ触るの?
Where do you touch yourself?
自分のどこを触るの?
自分のどこから触るの?
Body?
身体?
I don't like it!
嫌だ!
picture?
え?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
From the maid's mouth...
メイドさんの口からはやっぱ...
I can't say it.
言えない
Because the Moe Moe power will run away.
萌え萌えパワーが逃げちゃうから
Will you run away?
逃げちゃう?
See you later...
じゃあ後で...
It's moe now, but if it becomes erotic later, please let me know.
今萌え萌えだけど、後でエロエロになってきたら言ってね
Because it might contain some erotic power.
エロエロパワー入るかもしれないから
I've been asked to say that for so long.
そんなにずっと言ってもらうんで
Do you masturbate?
オナニするの?
オナニする?
Do it.
するんだ
What do you think?
どうだろう?
I will.
するね
refer to?
指?
Toys?
おもちゃ?
What are you having as a side dish?
何をおかずにしてるの?
picture?
え?
secret.
秘密
Are you having something outrageous as a side dish?
とんでもないものをおかずにしてるの?
I haven't.
してない
She's a little too cute, and I'd like to talk to her more.
ちょっと可愛すぎて、 もっといろいろ喋りたいんですけど、
I wanted to get started right away.
もう ちょっと早速ね、 始めちゃいたいと思って
I'm going to prepare something a little more beautiful this time.
今一回ちょっとキレイな準備してくるんで、
Can I have you wait just a little while?
ちょっとだけ待ってもらっていいですか?
Yes, I'm ready.
はい、準備できました
I want to get ready.
準備しちゃいたい
Were you not masturbating?
オナニしてなかった?
I haven't.
してないです
So let's really get started.
じゃあ、本当に始めます
Before we start, a word.
始まる前に、 一言
One word?
一言?
I say it and I'll repeat it.
僕が言うんで、 それを繰り返します
Is it the same?
同じの?
Say it cutely.
可愛く言ってね
Looks like a maid.
メイドさんっぽくね
Today, I asked my husband to take pictures of me in a lot of naughty places.
今日は、 ご主人様に、 いっぱいエッチなところを撮影してもら
I'm here.
います
picture?
え?
I'll ask you to take a picture.
撮 影してもらいます
Kyun!
キュン!
Like.
みたいな
Today, I will show you a lot of naughty things for my master.
今日は、 ご主人様に、 いっぱいエッチなところを、
I'll have you take lots of pictures.
沢山、 撮影してもらいます
Kyun!
キ ュン!
So cute!
かわいいー!
Good!
いいっす!
My heart was ruptured.
心臓が破裂された
It's embarrassing when people say Altama.
恥ずかしいアルタマって言われると
Kyun!
キュン!
So, can we really start now?
じゃあ、 もう本当に始めていいかな?
Are you mentally prepared?
心の準備大丈夫?
yes.
はい
Is it possible?
いけそう?
Yeah.
うん
You're a maid, do you have this service?
メイドさんでさ、 これサービスあるの?
do not have.
ない
That's good.
いいっすね
Seriously though.
ちょっとマジで
I'm really excited.
めっちゃキュンキュンしちゃってる
I'm so excited.
キュンキュンしちゃってる
Husband.
ご主人
Master, please say "gyu".
ご主人様、ギューって言ってきて
No, that's terrible.
いや ぁー やばい
I want to fulfill my dream of being a maid.
俺の夢をさ、 メイドさんってことはしたい
I'm full of dreams, so can you please change them?
夢が つまっているから、 ち なえてもらっていい?
Master, please say "gyu".
ご主人様、ギューって言ってきて
Master's tightness is dangerous, but
ご主人様のギュー ヤバいんだけど、
It's embarrassing, but it doesn't work. Is it working?
恥ずかしいんだけど 当たってない ヤバい 効いてる?
a little bit
ちょっと
You're going crazy when you're the owner of the camera. That's crazy.
カ メラのご主人様にと発狂しちゃうね ヤバい
A little in the opposite direction, in the opposite direction?
ちょっと 反対向き 反対向き?
The clothes are cute. Ena usually wears clothes like this. The fabric is nice too.
かわいいね、服 エナさんが普段こういう服着るんだ 生地もいい
Hey, is the fabric good too?
ね 生地もいい?
The fabric is good too
生地もいいよ
It's like we're taking a photo together. Cheki?
一 緒にチェキを撮ってる感じで チェキ?
Don't you have a check like this?
こういう感じのチェキないの?
do not have
ない
How many couples are there?
コ ーパーあるね 何カップル?
About F?
Fぐらい F?
It's really dangerous
めっちゃヤバいじゃん
I'll see more later
後 でいっぱい見ますよ
I've already carried it away, as much as I can
もう さらえてるよ、思いっきりでも
Your style is nice, and your skin is white. Try stretching your legs once.
ス タイルいいよね 肌白いしね 一回足伸ばしてみて
A little bit dark
ちょっと こりっと
I can stretch my legs a lot
して めっちゃ足伸べる
You're stepping on it with your feet, right? You don't know. You don't know.
足 で踏んだりしてるでしょ 知ってないよ 知 ってない
Where is the raw liver?
生 肝体どこ?
Raw liver body?
生肝体?
I don't get it, it tickles. It must feel good. It tickles.
分かんない くすぐったい 気持ちいいんだろ くすぐったい
Where are you being dragged?
ど こさられてる?
Where do you think you are being missed?
どこさられてると思う?
I don't like it
言って 嫌だ
what?
何?
Well, mom, stretch your legs a little.
じゃあ、 お母さん ちょっとガロンとして 足伸ばして
I don't like it, I'm embarrassed. What's wrong?
嫌 だ、恥ずかしい どうしたの?
No, I like sideways views of bras. I see. I want to see this.
違うよ ブラの横見も好きなんですよ なるほどね ここ見たい
of?
の?
what?
何?
What is it?
何 なの?
Look, it's really a horizontal shot. Look again.
見て 本当に横撮ってる もう一回見て
Are you angry?
怒 った?
forgive me
許して
It's really big
本当 にデカいね
Sorry, did I make a mistake?
ご めん 間違えちゃった?
I got caught, I got caught, I shouldn't have looked at it.
引っかかっちゃった 引っかかっちゃった 見ようといけなかった
But wait for another chance.
んだ けど もう一回チャンス待って
I got caught and almost dropped my camera. I got panicked.
引 っかかって、カメラ落とそうなった 焦っちゃった
nothing nothing
なん もない 何もない
Look, come down once.
見て 一回下来て
picture?
え?
That's fine. I'll check it out for myself. I'll check it out.
もう いい それは自分だけ 確かめる 確かめるよ
It looks beautiful.
綺 麗なっぽいだね
I'm being teased
そ ばれてる
When did it start to get bigger?
大 きくなってきた いつかな?
I don't know. Since when have you been wearing it unevenly?
分かんない ムラいつからつけてるの?
Unevenness?
ムラ?
Elementary school, high school age and above Reverse
小学校、高学年代 それぐらいから 逆
If you were big, would you like to be seen?
に 大きかったらさ 見られたりしたいの?
picture?
え?
No, do you want to?
しない したい?
Are you being watched? Are you being watched?
見られてる 見られてるの?
I'm in trouble
困った
Which do you prefer: being able to drink or being able to drink?
飲 められるのと 飲められるのどっちが好き?
Can you drink either one?
どっちかって どっちか 飲められるの?
Can I drink it?
飲められるの?
Can you hold your penis?
ちんこはさめる?
I don't know, let's try it then.
分かんない 試してみようか じゃあ、
Shall I lick it?
なめようか
Can you be criticized for being different?
ち がうとこなめられる なめられるの?
No, no, what kind of licking is that?
ち がう やだ どこのなめられると?
Master, please drink it.
主人様、ちくび飲めて
Master, please drink.
主 人様、ちくび飲めて
I did it
や った
Did you do it after enjoying your eyes?
お 目を楽しんだ後は したかな?
Dislike
嫌
It's starting to streak. I don't like it.
だ すじてきてます 嫌だ
I don't like it
嫌 だ
I saw it
見 えちゃった
Lie down diagonally and rest on your elbows.
横 になって 斜めになって 肘ついてみて
stretch your legs
足 伸ばして
what up?
どう した?
secret no
秘密 違う
I don't like it
嫌 だ
fully visible
丸 見え
Where is it spread?
ど こ広げられてますか?
What?
なん て?
You don't like it?
嫌だ なんて?
I haven't said anything. I need to say it again.
なんも言ってない もう一回言わないと
What do you do?
どう するの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Did you say it lightly?
軽くいった?
Yes, I would like you to tell me one thing.
うん 一個 教えてほしいんだけど
What should I put?
何 を入れる?
hole?
穴?
It's a hole to put everything in. I don't like it.
全部入れる穴です 嫌だ
Put your finger in the hole where you put your dick in
チ ンチン入れる穴に 指入れて
Medium Very weak
中 めっちゃ弱い
Chest was easy to move
胸 いけやすかった
It's just a fluke
気 まぐれじゃん
Can I lick it?
舐 めていい?
Tomorrow, rest on my elbow
明日俺の肘のっけて
That's why I'm going right away
だから すぐ行くんだね
elbow
肘 をつ
Please take it.
いて 頂戴して
I can't take it anymore, can you take it off?
もう 我慢できない 脱がしてくれる?
Okay, just the front here.
じゃあさ 前だけで こっち
Please do it
で してよ
what up?
どう した?
I don't understand
分かんない
In that state, look at me and make a piece with both hands.
その 状態で こっち見ながら 両手でピースして
Can I come in now?
そ ろそろ入れていい?
Can I put it in raw? Okay?
生で入れていいかな いい?
There's one thing I want you to say, so open your legs and do a double piece.
一個言ってほしい言葉があって 足開けて ダブルピースして し
Please put master's raw penis in your pussy.
な がら おまんこに ご主人様の生のおちんち 入れてください
Weak
弱 いじゃん
Take the challenge
挑 戦して
difficult?
難 しい?
spread your legs
足開けて
hands behind your back
手 を後ろにして
It was moving
動 いてやがった
Do your best to fill your pussy with master's sperm.
お まんこに ご主人様の精子いっぱい 頑張って
Inside full
中 でいっぱ
It's gone, I have to write it down.
い 出ちゃった 書き出さないと
Hey, can you feel it coming out from inside?
ね 中から出てる感じ分かった?
Did you do this?
これしたか?
Sixx in front of the camera is positive, then we'll talk about the last part later.
カメラの前でのシックスは ポジテンス じゃあ後で 最後の話でしょう